seolab.com 2016-11-06

# Softnik Technologies: Privacy Policy

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used.

## No Spyware / No Adware

All our software products are free from spyware or adware of any kind. Our products will never install any tracking software on your system, or collect personal information about you and your browsing habits. Our software does not "spy" on other programs you run or web sites you visit.

## The Information We Collect (through standard web log files)

You can visit the websites of Softnik Technologies (Softnik) without revealing any information about yourself. Softnik does collect information regarding visitors to our Web site, such as IP Address, number of visits, and average time spent through the standard web log files. We analyze this data for trends and statistics to help us improve the content of our site.

We have a number of free software that you may download from our site. Many of these software require no registration. This means that we will not even ask for your email address. You can simply download and use the software with out revealing any thing about yourself. These software will have a 'No registration' message displayed very near to the download link.

## Personal Information

There are times, however, when we may request information from you, such as your, name, address and e-mail address. When additional information is requested, we will try to let you know at the time of collection how we intend to use the personal information you provide, such as respond to your inquiry, participate in certain promotions, conduct a survey or allow you to access specific information. If you sign up for an Softnik electronic newsletter or e-mail list, each message will include instructions on how to "unsubscribe" from that list. We respect your right to choose whether to give us personal information or "opt out" if you do not wish to disclose personal information. We do our best to maintain the accuracy of any personal information you do supply to us.

Any information provided by you will be used for Softnik's purposes only. Your information will not be shared with individual or other companies [such as direct mail organizations or other third parties] unless required by law. However, Softnik may need to provide your name and delivery address to third parties that Softnik uses for delivering specific services to you (such as support services or shipping purposes when you ask us to send something to you).

Our Web sites may provide links to third party sites. Since we do not control those Web sites, we encourage you to review the privacy policies of these third party sites.

## Security and Quality

Softnik is committed to taking reasonable steps to protect the individual identifying information that you provide. You can help Softnik update and maintain the accuracy of any personal information you supply by notifying Softnik of any changes to your address, title, phone number or e-mail address. In some programs, you may do this online by following the instructions on membership profile pages. You may also update your information by contacting us with a description or example of what you wish to change.

## Cookies

Softnik some times uses cookies to allow us to provide you with tailored information from our Web. A cookie is an element of data that a Web site can send to your browser, which may then store it on your system. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether to accept it. These cookies do not track individual information. Softnik may also use cookies when you register for one of our products or services. In this case, a cookie will store useful information that enables our Web site to remember you when you return to visit, but only Softnik web sites can read that information. While using our websites, you may receive cookies from our advertisers or sponsors. Softnik does not control such cookies.

## Private membership sites

Software products that include access to one or more private membership sites may contain a _**quick access**_ button. Clicking the button will open the default Internet browser and automatically log you in to the private membership area. A valid authentication is required for this purpose. This is done by sending, to the server, a simple encrypted signature containing the current time-stamp and your product registration keycode that was supplied to you after purchase. This is applicable only if you have **purchased a software product** that includes access to one or more private membership sites and have successfully **registered the software** on your computer using the registration keycode provided by us.

## Oversight or Questions

Softnik welcomes comments and questions on this policy. As stated above, we are dedicated to protecting your privacy and will make every reasonable effort to keep your information secure. Due to the rapidly evolving changes on the Internet, we may update this policy. All revisions will be posted to this site. Please contact us if you have any questions regarding our policy.

This policy was last updated on November 18 2007
